Hello friends, my name is Sachin and I have
brought a video for you
on your own channel's network. Friends, today
I have brought the third video of Seven Stores in
front of you. So let's see which is
that top. Friends, this stock can become
multi-barrel in the coming time. The fundamentals are
quite strong. Let's see
which is that stop. Before that, friends, if you are
new to our channel, then along with subscribing to the channel, do
press the bell icon so that
you do not miss any important notification in the coming time.
Fellow friends of the channel,
links to some very good videos are
given in the description box. These are very educational
videos, so you should also watch them. You will
learn a lot. Do not miss it at all. So
friends, let's see
which stock is that.
So friends, first of all we will talk
about the value of this company and its fundamentals.
After that, we will see which
price you have to start clicking on it. So,
let's see what is its name. The
name of that stock is Pidilite
Industries Limited. It belongs to the large cap sector. Its price is Rs.
4878.  The house was
built on this day in 1528, the same house was
built in 20187, if I talk about one year, then
within one year it already gave a
U-turn of opposite 80%, friends,
if someone repairs such a huge downfall, someone else
reduces it, friends, then it means the
fundamentals of this company are very strong,
friends, if I talk to you about the affairs, then
in the face, you have converted the cable,
more than 170 pollutants stronger than Tubelight,
you have given it in it,
friends, and if we talk about its maximum,
friends, till now it has given opposite 800 to 1000 percent, then
friends, the potential
of this company is clearly visible, if we
talk about the elder sister of this company, then
friends,
you all must have heard yesterday, Fevicol is a very widely
used product, friends,
in furniture, after that,
you must have heard about Chemical Ahmed, whose name is used a lot in paper
industries and rubber industries,
this Doctor
Fixit, you must have seen it many times on your TV, I will
talk about it  Fabric also has a
lot of ads and you must have seen it on TV,
Feviquick twist, it is quite popular,
friends of Prince, M Still also has a
very big bank, friends, it deals
with many big brands, friends, its
biggest plus point, friends,
they have done so much advertising that
they have no competition, friends, with a lot of
attention and a lot of experimentation, they have
not found any place for it and that is why friends,
you have seen such a big growth in this company
and perhaps it will be so big that you will
see it in the company in the future also, the
biggest package is friends, the
management of this company, friends, if you do not
know how to know the management of any company,
then you should
like this video, I will
make the next video for you on how to find out
about the management of a company, so
friends, if we talk about this company, then first of all,
if I talk
about the victims, then Sacrifice of
Sixteen is around, that is
almost three from behind, friends, the
reason for this, friends, is simple that none of its
computers are good, otherwise many people are
elevation  We will meet again and it is
available for free on Amazon friends, no
negative effect is seen here after
drinking friends, friends, it is quite high, so the
reason for that is also the same friends, this division
uses it for a very good time, you will keep getting very good different products
here, now let me talk
about its financial trend,
you see, from 2016 to 2018, the
revenue and profit have
increased in a great way, friends, maybe
this time they will get a small dream here, so
friends, it is also available at an equally low price, so
you have to
start investing on it, which dress to invest in,
I will tell you, so
friends, look at the Financial Times, then you must have understood
how much profit the company
can show in the coming time, now talking
about its share holding pattern,
if I tell you the most post effect, then no
positive share holding is seen here,
friends, its promoters have
around 70%, whereas mutual funds
have around 3.39%, the
holding in the team's romantic institute is also
very high, friends  Keep in mind that
F5 Press has also done a very big job in this.
Friends, if I talk about total promoter holding,
you will see that growth in the last
6 quarters. So this is a very good thing.
Very positive news. Friends, if we
talk about its big competition, then there is
no big competitor available in the market. Atul Industries has
definitely given it some competition, but it has won that too by a very
big margin. Friends,
if we talk about its dividend,
Aishwarya Rusi, then friends,
it has produced a very good ROC.
Friends, the dividend is also around 5%. So
all the factors are positive for it. And
if I tell you the best thing, friends, the
company is completely debit-free, so this is the
best thing for this company. If you see at
which price you should
start clicking on it, if we talk about
its technical analyst, then if
I talk about the best indicators, then
MCD and RS
Shruti are very good indicators. If you think
that you do not know how to use them,
then I have provided links in the description.
You can watch those videos.  Look, you will learn a lot,
friends.
You should pick up these three - Embassy RSI and Bollinger Bands. The
links for all three are given in the description box,
so you should check them out. You will learn a lot. If
I talk about MCD, then in Embassy,
friends, there is no single signal here.
Very soon, we may see sell signals
because friends, this trend has been
consolidating for a long time. So, there are
chances of a very high
fall. Friends, from here you have to
wait a little once, a slight and
value do is ready and in this mirror,
friends, what happens is that a slight and
value has reached this level.
Hello friends, you should
not wait immediately, you have to wait a little
and that, but let me tell you for how long you have to do that. So,
friends, Bollinger Bands is a
very good indicator.
Friends, it has reached Davison here, so
the chances are very high that it will fall from here
and it will reach the price of 3004, friends. So,
you should start doing this for a minute,
friends.  From around 38k,
friends, you do not have to invest in bulk there also,
friends, you have to do only
such P i.e.
Systematic Investment Plan, buy on
dips, friends, rather never do it in management
and friends, your time should be a
little long,
you can get very good money here but do
not invest in it for a long time,
friends, keep a light presence on the people, you will get a lot of
problems here,
friends, first investment
friends, you have to do on 30, after that you can do
alignment friends, 2018, so
if you make one of your own, this dip pressed below 3000, then make a
light investment there, you will get
it quite good, so
friends, see you in the next video, till then
Baba, if you laugh in this video, then you
must like and share it.